Bloom Southwest Jewish Archives Arizona Reference Files, ca. 1850-1998 (bulk 1870-1970)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Levin, Alexander. (Box 5)
- Levin, Henry. (Box 5)
- Levit, Sady. (Box 5)
- Levkowitz, Bertie. (Box 5)
- Levkowitz, Clara. (Box 5)
- Levkowitz, Helene. (Box 5)
- Levkowitz family. (Box 5)
- Levkowitz, Milton. (Box 5)
- Levy, Aaron. (Box 5)
- Levy, Alfred. (Box 5)
- Levy, Ben (Ajo, AZ). (Box 5)
- Levy, Ben (Douglas, AZ). (Box 5)
- Levy, Ben (Winslow, AZ). (Box 5)
- Levy brothers (Mohave County, AZ). (Box 5)
- Levy, David. (Box 5)
- Levy's Department Store (Tucson). (Box 5)
- Levy, Donnie. (Box 5)
- Levy, Dora. (Box 5)
- Levy, Doug. (Box 5)
- Levy, Esther. (Box 5)
- Levy, Eugene H. (Box 5)
- Levy family. (Box 5)
- Levy, Felix. (Box 5)
- Levy, Ike. (Box 5)
- Levy, Isaac. (Box 5)
- Levy, Jacob. (Box 5)
- Levy, Jake. (Box 5)
- Levy, Jim. (Box 5)
- Levy, Joe. (Box 5)
- Levy, Leon. (Box 5)
- Levy, Chief Levy (Indian chief?). (Box 5)
- Levy, Lois. (Box 5)
- Levy, Mamie. (Box 5)
- Levy, Mary. (Box 5)
- Levy, Miguel and Norma. (Box 5)
- Levy, Mike. (Box 5)
- Levy, Moise. (Box 5)
- Levy, Nathan. (Box 5)
- Levy, Sam. (Box 5)
- Levy, Sol (Bisbee). (Box 6)
- Lewis, Howard. (Box 6)
- Lewis, Sol. (Box 6)
- Lewkowitz, Burton. (Box 6)
- Lewkowitz, Herman. (Box 6)
- Lewkowitz, Jerry. (Box 6)
- Lex, Michael. (Box 6)
- Liberman, Julius. (Box 6)
- Lichertman, Cantor Ivor. (Box 6)
- Lieb, Dr. Charles. (Box 6)
- Liese, Harry. (Box 6)
- Lipsey, Alfred. (Box 6)
- Lipshultz, Menachem. (Box 6)
- Lisitzky, Charles. (Box 6)
- Little Chapel of All Nations (Tucson). (Box 6)
- Littman, Sol. (Box 6)
- Loeb, Charles. (Box 6)
- Loewenstein, Ben. (Box 6)
- London, Rabbis Ross and Victoria. (Box 6)
- Lowenstein, I. (Box 6)
- Lo[e]wenstein, Manny. (Box 6)
- Louchheim, Rabbi Thomas. (Box 6)
- Lukin, Abe. (Box 6)
- Lukin/Sachs family. (Box 6)
- Lulley, Mark. (Box 6)
- Lyons, Abraham. (Box 6)
- Lyons, Isaac. (Box 6)
- Malach, Ruth. (Box 6)
- Maimonidean Society (University of Arizona) - 4f. (Box 6)
- Mallin, Sol. (Box 6)
- Manassee family. (Box 6)
- Mannassee, Herman (various spellings of surname). (Box 6)
- Mannis, David. (Box 6)
- Mansfeld, Eva. (Box 6)
- Mansfeld, Jacob S. (Box 6)
- Mansfeld, Leonor (married name: Williamson). (Box 6)
- Mansfeld, Samuel J. (Box 6)
- Mansfeld, Mrs. Samuel J. (Box 6)
- Mansfield, Monte. (Box 6)
- "Many Jews Helped the Pioneers Settle Arizona" (article). (Box 6)
- Marcus, Janet. (Box 6)
- Marcus, Robert. (Box 6)
- Marcus, Sadye Capin. (Box 6)
- Marcus, Sam. (Box 6)
- Marcus, Simon. (Box 6)
- Margolies, Lillian. (Box 6)
- Marks, Barnett. (Box 6)
- Marks, Jake. (Box 6)
- Marks, Max. (Box 6)
- Marks, Selma Paul. (Box 6)
- Marshall, Jonathan. (Box 6)
- Martin, Daniel. (Box 6)
- Marx, Abraham. (Box 6)
- Masonic Lodge (Tucson). (Box 6)
- May, Louis A. (Box 6)
- Mayer, Marcus B. (Box 6)
- Mayer, William P. (Box 6)
- McKenney's Business Directory -1882-1883 (excerpt - Arizona listings). (Box 6)
- Mecham, Gov. Evan. (Box 6)
- Mechles, Leon. (Box 6)
- Meckler, Steven. (Box 6)
- Medicine (Jews in). (Box 6)
- Meier, J. A. (Box 6)
- Melczer brothers. (Box 6)
- Melczer, Mrs. Ed. (Box 6)
- Melnick, Jacob. (Box 6)
- Mendel, Lillian. (Box 6)
- Merchants (Jewish). (Box 6)
- Meyer, Carrie. (Box 6)
- Meyer, Judge Charles. (Box 6)
- Meyer, Henry Jr. (Box 6)
- Meyer, Henry Sr. (Box 6)
- Meyer, Isadore. (Box 6)
- Meyer, A. Leonard. (Box 6)
- Miami, AZ. (Box 6)
- Miessner, Julia Allen. (Box 6)
- Migdal, Lila Z. Haas. (Box 6)
- Milberg, Morton and Helga. (Box 6)
- Miles, Harriet K. (Box 6)
- Military (Jews in). (Box 6)
- Miller, Ed. (Box 6)
- Miller, Mayor George. (Box 6)
- Miller, Jacob. (Box 6)
- Miller, Joe. (Box 6)
- Miller, Rachel Sadowsky. (Box 6)
- Miller, Zach. (Box 6)
- Millstone, Donald. (Box 6)
- Mining (Jews in). (Box 6)
- Mogill, Leo. (Box 6)
- Mohave County, AZ. (Box 6)
- Monsky, Thelma. (Box 6)
- Moore, Wendy Marmis. (Box 6)
- Morris, Abe P. (Box 6)
- Morris, Isaac. (Box 6)
- Morrison, Ray A. (Box 6)
- Mossman, Lettie. (Box 6)
- Murillo, Lupita. (Box 6)
- Myerson family. (Box 6)
- Myerson, Jean. (Box 6)
- Myerson, Joesph. (Box 6)
- Nathan, Dena. (Box 6)
- Nathan, Sol. (Box 6)
- National Council of Jewish Women (NCJW). (Box 6)
- Native Americans and Jews (relations). (Box 6)
- Neiblum, Lottie. (Box 6)
- Nemeroff, Celia. (Box 6)
- Netzky, Lester. (Box 6)
- Neugass, Joesph. (Box 6)
- Neustatter, Major Isidor. (Box 6)
- Nevins, James. (Box 6)
- Newman, Jack B. (Box 6)
- Newmark, Cecil. (Box 6)
- New Mexico. (Box 6)
- Nieblum, Henry. (Box 6)
- Niemoller, Pastor Martin. (Box 6)
- Noah, Max. (Box 6)
- Nogales, AZ. (Box 6)
- "Northern Arizona Territorial Death and Burial Records" (1870-1910). (Box 6)
- Novick, Herman. (Box 6)
- Oberfelder, S. (Box 6)
- Ogden, Emma. (Box 6)
- Oleisky, Rabbi Arthur. (Box 6)
- "On the Arizona-Sonora Frontier in 1880" (article). (Box 6)
- "Operation Exodus" (Tucson Jewish Federation). (Box 6)
- Oppenheimer, Ernest. (Box 6)
- Organization for Rehabilitation through Training (ORT). (Box 6)
- Ostroy, Irving. (Box 6)
- Owls Club (Tucson). (Box 6)
- Pakier, Freddi. (Box 6)
- Parents of North American Israelis (Tucson chapter). (Box 6)
- Peachin, David. (Box 6)
- Peck, Jeffery. (Box 6)
- Perkins, Judith. (Box 6)
- Perlin, Bernie. (Box 6)
- Perlman, Natran. (Box 6)
- Peterson, Cele. (Box 6)
- Phillips, Ed. (Box 6)
- Phoenix anti-semitism. (Box 6)
- "Phoenix aristocracy" (clipping). (Box 6)
- Phoenix - Arizona Jewish Historical Society (Phoenix Chapter). (Box 6)
- Phoenix B'nai B'rith organization. (Box 6)
- Phoenix City Council. (Box 6)
- Phoenix - "Greater Phoenix Jewish News". (Box 6)
- Phoenix Hebrew Academy. (Box 6)
- Phoenix history. (Box 6)
- Phoenix: the History of a Southwestern Metropolis (excerpt). (Box 6)
- Phoenix Jewish Community Center. (Box 6)
- Phoenix Jewish Federation. (Box 6)
- Phoenix - the Kishinef Fund. (Box 6)
- Phoenix Volunteer Fire Department. (Box 6)
- Pima County jurists. (Box 6)
- Pimeria Alta Historical Society. (Box 6)
- Pioneer Jews in the Southwest United States. (Box 6)
- "Pioneer Jews of Arizona" (article - Harriet Rochlin). (Box 6)
- Pitt, Donald. (Box 6)
- Plotkin, Albert and Sylvia. (Box 6)
- Plotkin, Irving. (Box 6)
- Polk, Frank -2f. (Box 7)
- Polk, Sally. (Box 7)
- Poplanshy, Pauline. (Box 7)
- Population surveys. (Box 7)
- Portman, Sophie. (Box 7)
- Posner, Philip. (Box 7)
- Posner, Robert. (Box 7)
- Postil, Eleanor. (Box 7)
- Pozez family. (Box 7)
- Prescott, AZ. (Box 7)
- Present, Elmer. (Box 7)
- Price, Louis. (Box 7)
- "Project Isaiah". (Box 7)
- Purim Ball (Tucson -1886). (Box 7)
- Rabin, Irving. (Box 7)
- Rabinowitz, Steve. (Box 7)
- Rado, Leanore Levy. (Box 7)
- Ramenofsky, Dorothy. (Box 7)
- Ramenofsky, Elizabeth. (Box 7)
- Ranching (Jews in). (Box 7)
- Rappaport, Harold. (Box 7)
- Raskin, Fannie. (Box 7)
- Rauh, Anna. (Box 7)
- Raykh/Weinstein/Yusofora families. (Box 7)
- Raykh, Vera V. (Box 7)
- Reimers, Rabbi Paula. (Box 7)
- Reich, Molly. (Box 7)
- Reiss, Leni. (Box 7)
- Republican Party politics. (Box 7)
- Resnick, Dr. Sol. (Box 7)
- Reznik, Michael. (Box 7)
- Reznikov, Dr. Anna. (Box 7)
- Riback, Jack. (Box 7)
- Rickles, Abraham. (Box 7)
- "Rings" of influence in Arizona history. (Box 7)
- Ritchie, Matthew. (Box 7)
- Rivera, Geraldo. (Box 7)
- Robinson, J.B. (Box 7)
- Rochlin, Abe. (Box 7)
- Rochlin, Annie Shapiro. (Box 7)
- Rochlin, Claire. (Box 7)
- Rochlin, Fred. (Box 7)
- Rochlin, Harriet. (Box 7)
- Rochlin, Sidney. (Box 7)
- Ronald, Rabbi Jeffrey N. (Box 7)
- "Roots in the Desert..." (title of a photographic exhibition). (Box 7)
- Rosen, Babette. (Box 7)
- Rosen, Fred. (Box 7)
- Rosen, Judith. (Box 7)
- Rosenbaum, Marcia. (Box 7)
- Rosenbaum, Morris C. (Box 7)
- Rosenbaum, Polly. (Box 7)
- Rosenberg, Mrs. Morris. (Box 7)
- Rosenberg, Selma. (Box 7)
- Rosenberg, Seth. (Box 7)
- Rosenberg, William. (Box 7)
- Rosenberg, Winfield. (Box 7)
- Rosenblatt, Paul. (Box 7)
- Rosenblum, Hyman. (Box 7)
- Rosenbluth, Mike. (Box 7)
- Rosenfeld, Bernath. (Box 7)
- Rosenstein, Herman. (Box 7)
- Rosenstern, Louis. (Box 7)
- Rosentstock, Alberto. (Box 7)
- Rosenthal, Joseph. (Box 7)
- Rosenthal, N. (Box 7)
- Rosenthal, Sandy. (Box 7)
- Rosenzweig, Arline ("Sandy"). (Box 7)
- Rosenzweig, Harry. (Box 7)
- Rosenzweig, Hillel. (Box 7)
- Rosenzweig, Isaac. (Box 7)
- Rosenzweig, Rosa. (Box 7)
- Rothberger, Jeannette. (Box 7)
- Rothman, Martha K. (Box 7)
- Rothschild Ice Cream Shop. (Box 7)
- Rubin, Dan. (Box 7)
- Rubin, William J. (Box 7)
- Rubinstein, Irving and Harriet. (Box 7)
- Rubinstein, Joesph. (Box 7)
- Rubinow, Thelma. (Box 7)
- Rudnitsky, Alex. (Box 7)
- Ruggil, Solomon. (Box 7)
- Rulney, Melynda. (Box 7)
- Rutz, Rebecca Staman and Myer Lawrence. (Box 7)
- Sachs, Dr. Jacob Leonard. (Box 7)
- Sachs, Woolf. (Box 7)
- Sacks, Dr. Benjamin. (Box 7)
- Safford, AZ. (Box 7)
- Saft, Ralph. (Box 7)
- Salonic, Philip. (Box 7)
- Samter, J. (Box 7)
- Sandoval, Juan. (Box 7)
- Sare, Moysey. (Box 7)
- Sarver, Jack. (Box 7)
- Sattler, Esther. (Box 7)
- Satz, Wayne. (Box 7)
- Schaefer, Helen S. (Box 7)
- Schaefer, John Paul. (Box 7)
- Schain, Abraham. (Box 7)
- Schain, Al. (Box 7)
- Schantz, Mildred. (Box 7)
- Schenkner, Howard. (Box 7)
- Schiesel, Herman. (Box 7)
- Schiff, Nathan. (Box 7)
- Schifman, David. (Box 7)
- Schlomowitz, Fanny. (Box 7)
- Schneider, Eleanor. (Box 7)
- Schneider, William. (Box 7)
- Schoenfeld, Louis. (Box 7)
- Schonholz, Hertz. (Box 7)
- Schulman, Edmund and Alsie. (Box 7)
- Schurgin, Samuel. (Box 7)
- Schuster family. (Box 7)
- Schwartz, Moritz. (Box 7)
- Sedley, Bernard. (Box 7)
- Sedona, AZ. (Box 7)
- Sehler, Jeff Hannan. (Box 7)
- Seidel, Jonathan. (Box 7)
- Seidner, Dr. Aaron. (Box 7)
- Seligman, Theodore. (Box 7)
- Seligmann, C. (Box 7)
- Senderoff, Charles. (Box 7)
- Senor, Irving and Rachel. (Box 7)
- Sephardim of Tucson. (Box 7)
- Shandling, Garry. (Box 7)
- Shanhouse, Morris. (Box 7)
- Shapiro, A.D. (Box 7)
- Shapiro, Norman. (Box 7)
- Shapiro, Sam. (Box 7)
- Shayevich, Sergey. (Box 7)
- Sheinbein, Melvin ("Mickey"). (Box 7)
- Shemtov, Rabbi Joesph. (Box 7)
- Sherberg, Esther. (Box 7)
- Sherman, Rose. (Box 7)
- Sherwin, Rabbi Richard. (Box 7)
- Shiff family. (Box 7)
- Shiff, Murray. (Box 7)
- Shifrin family. (Box 7)
- Shore, Sean Marc. (Box 7)
- Shostac, Lillian Ilitzky. (Box 7)
- Shrager, Nancy. (Box 7)
- Shropshire, Donald Gray. (Box 7)
- Siebenberg, Harry. (Box 7)
- Siegel, Rabbi Kenneth. (Box 7)
- Siegel, Shirley Ruth. (Box 7)
- Silberman, Rabbi Herbert. (Box 7)
- Silberman, Rabbi Lou. (Box 7)
- Silver, Diane. (Box 7)
- Silver, Rose. (Box 7)
- Silverbell Road (Tucson - found objects). (Box 7)
- Silverberg, Simon. (Box 7)
- Silverman, Estherlea. (Box 7)
- Silverman, Lisa. (Box 7)
- Silverman, Ruth. (Box 7)
- Silverstein, Milt. (Box 7)
- Silverstone, Sally. (Box 7)
- Simon, Abraham. (Box 7)
- Simon, Bertha. (Box 7)
- Simon, Morris. (Box 7)
- Simon, Rabbi Ralph. (Box 7)
- Singer, Isaac. (Box 7)
- Singer, Mark. (Box 7)
- Slamon, Judge J.J. (Box 7)
- Slavkin, Tillie. (Box 7)
- Smith, Herbert. (Box 7)
- Smythe, Patricia. (Box 7)
- Society for Crypto-Judaic Studies. (Box 7)
- Solomon, Adolph. (Box 7)
- Solomon, Anna. (Box 7)
- Solomon, Charles. (Box 7)
- Solomon, David. (Box 7)
- Solomon family. (Box 7)
- Solomon, Hattie (Mrs. Charles). (Box 7)
- Solomon, Hyman. (Box 7)
- Solomon, Isidor Elkan. (Box 7)
- Solomon/Lesinsky/Freudenthal families. (Box 7)
- Solomon, Max. (Box 7)
- Solomon, Ruth. (Box 7)
- Solomonville, AZ. (Box 7)
- Solot, Ben H. (Box 7)
- Solot family. (Box 7)
- Solot, Marian. (Box 7)
- Solot, Morton. (Box 7)
- Sonder, Anne. (Box 7)
- Sonoita kosher wine production. (Box 7)
- Southwest Jewish Archives (conference - 1991). (Box 7)
- "Southwest Jewish History" (newsletter of the Southwest Jewish Archives). (Box 7)
- Soza family (newsletter). (Box 7)
- Specter, Sam and Miriam. (Box 7)
- Spielberg, Steven. (Box 7)
- Spitalny family. (Box 7)
- Spivack, Marvin. (Box 7)
- Staab and Company. (Box 7)
- Stein family. (Box 7)
- Stein, Max. (Box 7)
- Steinfeld, Albert. (Box 7)
- Steinfeld, Albert. (Box 8)
- Steinfeld, Irene (married name: Pizzini). (Box 8)
- Steinfeld, Viola (married name: O'Neil). (Box 8)
- Sterling, Irene. (Box 8)
- Stern, Sarah. (Box 8)
- Stickle, Leonard. (Box 8)
- St. Johns, AZ. (Box 8)
- Stocker, Joseph. (Box 8)
- Stone Avenue Temple Project (Tucson). (Box 8)
- Stone, Harry. (Box 8)
- Strauss, Charles M. (Box 8)
- Strauss, Gerd. (Box 8)
- Strober, Harry. (Box 8)
- Strug, Dr. Burt. (Box 8)
- Strug, Kerri. (Box 8)
- Stuart, Yale. (Box 8)
- Sverdlik, Henrietta. (Box 8)
- Swetschinski, Daniel M. (Box 8)
- Syde, Saul H. (Box 8)
- Sylvia Plotkin Judaica Museum (at Temple Beth El - Phoenix). (Box 8)
- Taren, Elizabeth. (Box 8)
- Temple Beth Israel (Phoenix) - 2f. (Box 8)
- Temple Beth Shalom (Green Valley). (Box 8)
- Temple Beth Shalom (Havasu). (Box 8)
- Temple B'rith Shalom (Prescott). (Box 8)
- Temple Emanu-El (Tempe). (Box 8)
- Temple Emanu-El (Tucson). (Box 8)
- Temple Kol Hamidbar (Sierra Vista). (Box 8)
- Temple of Music and Art (Tucson). (Box 8)
- Temple Solel (Paradise Valley). (Box 8)
- Terman, Ruth. (Box 8)
- Tishkevich, Nina. (Box 8)
- "To Tender Our Services" (excerpt from The Arizona Rough Riders). (Box 8)
- Tobin, Irwin. (Box 8)
- Tobin, Saul. (Box 8)
- Tombstone, AZ. (Box 8)
- Tombstone (AZ) Jewish cemetery. (Box 8)
- Torme, Arthur. (Box 8)
- Tribolet, Godfrey. (Box 8)
- Tuba City, AZ. (Box 8)
- Tucson, AZ. (Box 8)
- Tucson (Chabad-Lubavitch sect). (Box 8)
- Tucson (city council). (Box 8)
- Tucson (city directory -1881). (Box 8)
- Tucson (city government). (Box 8)
- Tucson (downtown map/Jewish homes). (Box 8)
- Tucson (first Jewish wedding in Territory of Arizona). (Box 8)
- Tucson (Hanukkah celebration). (Box 8)
- Tucson Hebrew Academy. (Box 8)
- Tucson Hebrew High School. (Box 8)
- Tucson (historical homes). (Box 8)
- Tucson Jewish Cemetery Association, 1890. (Box 8)
- Tucson Jewish Community Center - 2f. (Box 8)
- Tucson Jewish Community Center (Maccabi youth athletic team). (Box 8)
- Tucson Jewish Community Council. (Box 8)
- Tucson ("The Jewish Community In Tucson: Structure and Forms of Jewish Self-Identification" - article). (Box 8)
- Tucson Jewish Family and Children's Service. (Box 8)
- Tucson Jewish Film Festival. (Box 8)
- Tucson Jewish War Veterans. (Box 8)
- Tucson (Jewish welfare and benevolent societies). (Box 8)
- Tucson (Jewish youth study). (Box 8)
- Tucson (Kosher meat products). (Box 8)
- Tucson ("Landmarks of the Old Pueblo" - historical sketches). (Box 8)
- Tucson: The Life and Times of an American City (excerpt). (Box 8)
- Tucson (map -1862; copy of). (Box 8)
- Tucson (mayors of). (Box 8)
- Tucson (newspaper of 1879; notes taken from). (Box 9)
- Tucson ("Tent City"). (Box 9)
- Tucson (World War II). (Box 9)
- Tuller, Mort and Howard. (Box 9)
- Tumarkin, Linda. (Box 9)
- Turken, Morris. (Box 9)
- United Order of True Sisters (Tucson). (Box 9)
- University of Arizona (anti-semitism). (Box 9)
- University of Arizona (Hillel Foundation). (Box 9)
- University of Arizona (history). (Box 9)
- University of Arizona (Holocaust denial issues). (Box 9)
- University of Arizona (Jewish athletes). (Box 9)
- University of Arizona (Judaic Studies Program). (Box 9)
- University of Arizona (Saudi Arabia relations). (Box 9)
- Uvaydova, Sarah. (Box 9)
- Veksler, Eugene. (Box 9)
- Vertlieb, Freda. (Box 9)
- Vicenzi, Richard. (Box 9)
- Villa, Pancho. (Box 9)
- Viner, Andy. (Box 9)
- Volgy, Thomas J. (Box 9)
- Wallet, Eleanor Ruth. (Box 9)
- Wartsky, Bernard. (Box 9)
- Wasserman, Celma. (Box 9)
- Weinberger, Jacob. (Box 9)
- Weiner, Leonard. (Box 9)
- Weinstein, Harry. (Box 9)
- Weinstein, Jeffrey Neil. (Box 9)
- Weinstein, Joseph. (Box 9)
- Weinstein, Rebecca. (Box 9)
- Weintraub, Anna R. (Box 9)
- Weintraub, Ron and Diane. (Box 9)
- Weisberg, Sheldon. (Box 9)
- Weisl, Bernard. (Box 9)
- Weisl, Sig. (Box 9)
- Weiss, Devora. (Box 9)
- Weiss, Melissa. (Box 9)
- Weissman, Eva. (Box 9)
- Weisz, Elsa. (Box 9)
- Weisz, Kurt. (Box 9)
- Weizenbaum, Suzanne. (Box 9)
- Weizenbaum, Rabbi Joesph. (Box 9)
- Welisch, T. (Box 9)
- Wernick family. (Box 9)
- Wertheimer, Aaron. (Box 9)
- Wesendorff, Max. (Box 9)
- Wetzler, Julius. (Box 9)
- Weyler, Charles. (Box 9)
- Whitehill, Lorraine. (Box 9)
- Wickenberg, AZ. (Box 9)
- Wiener, David. (Box 9)
- Wiesel, Elie. (Box 9)
- Wilf, Regina. (Box 9)
- Willcox, AZ. (Box 9)
- Williams, AZ. (Box 9)
- Wine, David S. (Box 9)
- Winter, Charles F. (Box 9)
- Wintner, Gertrude. (Box 9)
- Wise, Joesph E. (Box 9)
- Wisotsky, Jerry. (Box 9)
- Wolf, Harry. (Box 9)
- Wolf, Ida. (Box 9)
- Wolfe, Ivan. (Box 9)
- Wolfe, Michelle Pinnas. (Box 9)
- Wollenberg, Charles. (Box 9)
- Wollenberg family. (Box 9)
- Wollenberg, Louis. (Box 9)
- Wolpert, Saul. (Box 9)
- Woolf, Eta. (Box 9)
- Wolsky, Sam and Bobbie. (Box 9)
- Wormser, Michael. (Box 9)
- Yakorevsky, Vladimir. (Box 9)
- Yall, Anna. (Box 9)
- Yavelberg, Samuel. (Box 9)
- Yontef, Roger. (Box 9)
- Yontef, Samuel. (Box 9)
- Yusufova, Almas. (Box 9)
- Zales, Ruth. (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf, Aaron. (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf family. (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf (Lilienfeld sisters). (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf, Fanny. (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf, Julia. (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf, Lina. (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf, Louis. (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf, Mathilde. (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf/Steinfeld families. (Box 9)
- Zeckendorf, William. (Box 9)
- Zuckerman, Mel and Enid. (Box 9)